Hello everyone!
I'm Mizuki Hiraoka from Hyuhizaka46.
I'm at home right now.
This March, the Hokuriku Shinkansen line was extended.
I can now go home from Tokyo by one train from my hometown, Tsurugama.
At last!
I would like to take the Hokuriku Shinkansen to go back to Fukui.
I'm going back to Fukui!
Yay!
It's been a long time since I've been back home after New Year's, but
I'm really looking forward to it!
I'm going to enjoy my trip home as much as I can!
Next stop: Kagawa line!
We'll be waiting for you!
We've arrived at Tsuruga Station!
Hello!
It's my first time here.
It's totally different from before
I was like, "Is this really Tsuruga?
It's so hot! The weather is really nice.
It's usually cloudy in Hokuriku.
I wasn't sure if it would clear up.
But it's really sunny!
I found it!
In a black light truck.
In the black light truck, there's a father with black sunglasses.
With a father in black sunglasses.
I'm home.
Put this in the back.
You can put this inside.
I got it.
Here we go.
I'm home.
It's been a long time since New Year's.
Yeah...
Isn't your hair shorter?
Shorter than usual.
It's been like this lately.
I see.
Are you listening to this? It's in the back.
It's a window.
It looks great.
Good night. - Good night.
See you later.
I'm home.
I'm home!
Haku-chan
Hi, sweetie
Cute
Long time no see
Come here
You don't like it? Now?
Now?
No?
Don't like it.
No.
Have you been there recently? Aoba prefecture.
I haven't been.
No.
No, I haven't.
You went to Seoul with Jol.
No, we didn't.
I'm not going.
It's fine. It's just for when you come back.
I see.
Mountains.
It's so mountainous.
Yeah, they're green all the way up there.
The background doesn't change at all.
Oh, I see what you mean.
It's a little bit, it's beautiful.
It's really pretty green.
No, no, no.
The green is cute.
The deep bathing.
The deep is lush
I'm in the European area
I'm here at Tsuruga Ekimae.
I'm going to eat
Petro, isn't it?
Thank you.
Here we are.
Looks too good.
Bon appétit.
HAYA
Dick
me ni
me
I want everyone to try it!
Delicious!
Good morning.
I'm going to my grandmother's house now.
And give her some gifts.
After that, I'd like to go to the Rainbow Line.
I haven't seen my grandma since New Year's.
It's been a while.
I hope she's well.
Hey! I'm home!
Here's a video I'm taking.
I'm doing well!
I'm fine!
Oh, my gosh!
Oh my God!
It's so hot.
Can I take a bath?
Yes, can I? On the contrary.
I'll try not to take too many pictures.
I was lying on my side.
I was asleep. I'm sorry.
I'm home.
Here you go.
I brought you something.
Oh, man, I'm always sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
How are you? How are you?
I'm good.
How are you?
Good.
I've been trying to go to karaoke lately.
Karaoke?
I've been going to karaoke since last September.
Eisaku Okawa is a surprisingly good singer.
That's right.
Like this... Like this...
This is how we made the karaoke lights.
You see the songs on this side?
I'll write the score.
I really think it's going to be 90.
That's great!
I thought it was going to be 90.
That's great.
Nine hundred.
I thought it was going to be 90.
You're going to Suzuka? You're free to go.
And you know what?
Free time.
About 30 songs per person.
What!
30?
That's amazing.
Thirty.
So young.
Look at you all, 89 and up, huh?
All you get are high scores.
They're all high scores, aren't they?
80, 90, 90, 90, 90, 90, 90...
You know what I mean?
Grandpa?
Grandpa.
How many steps to 90?
That's amazing. - Yeah.
87 or something, right?
That's amazing.
You know what?
I'm awake.
I'm awake, and the teacher says karaoke is good. He says, "Please sing as much as you can.
He said, "If you sing for 2 hours, you can sing for 480 yen for an hour.
I get a phone call. It's time to go. That's just annoying. That's why.
You go free. You go as a freebie, right? If you go as a freebie, it's normally 891 yen per person. Free.
It's a little expensive now. It's summer vacation. Even in Bonn, it's not expensive.
Mi-chan goes there sometimes. You see? You've been singing karaoke, karaoke, karaoke, karaoke, karaoke, karaoke. It's true. I go to karaoke. I go about 5 times a month. I go about 5 times a month. Isn't this place great?
This place. This place. Mi-chan has been doing this for a long time. Oh, consecutive. That's great.
She said her squats are going well, too.
That's good, that's good.
She's already having fun.
That's good.
Mi-chan, you're going to be beautiful, aren't you?
Mittenyan. Keep on getting better and better and making notes for Mitsuki.
I'm so happy.
Hey, Hinata-chan.
You've been showing it to me for a long time.
Drawing like this all the time.
This is how I've been doing that thing you did.
I've been writing the blogs in order.
You're done here?
Yes, I did.
You've only written up to the stars?
You've been writing this for a long time.
What's your latest blog?
This is all that comes up.
It's so cool.
So this is how you write about what people are doing to you.
I'm glad.
Yeah, I'm glad.
Here you go.
That's great.
My sister wrote that.
Amazing.
Hyugaizaka Notebook
Hinatazaka Notebook
Thank you!
I watch YouTube all the time.
You're doing a great job.
That's amazing.
I'm proud of you.
I'm having fun. - Are you having fun?
I'm having so much fun.
I'm so proud of you.
You're gonna have so much fun!
You too
You're so young.
No matter how many times I do it...
I can't remember.
It's stressful.
If I make a mistake, it'll be a mess.
I thought it was great.
That's great.
Hey, man.
I'll do my best! See you later!
Thank you!
Oh, my God!
Where are you going now?
The electric department's painting is beautiful, and the weather's beautiful.
It's beautiful weather! It's gonna be a beautiful day!
You should go!
Hey, you, bring me this.
Thank you.
I'm sorry. Thank you.
Come again.
Thank you. See you later.
I'm off.
Take care, Chika-chan.
I'm so happy.
It's hot.
Thank you. See you again. I'll be back.
Let me know how it goes.
Thank you. See you soon. Thank you.
You're here.
You're right.
Too powerful.
It's so easy.
That's great.
You look the same as always.
You're looking good.
Bon appétit.
Ahh!
It's on the hot spring.
I'm scared.
I'm on a hot spring!
I've been on a hot spring for quite a while.
I've been on a hot spring.
Wow!
That's a lot of iron.
Wow...
Gong, gong, gong.
Yay!
We're here!
Thank you very much.
We're here.
Oh, look at this.
That medallion looks delicious.
But, I mean, is that what I think it is? Oh, my God.
This is bad.
But, Mi-chan's place is like this.
Isn't it?
Ki and Ш?
I'll take it.
Thank you very much.
I'll eat outside.
I can see more than that.
Wow.
Black butterflies.
That's so cool.
I'm so excited.
It's not spreading, is it?
There it is!
Ta-da!
Oh, yeah!
Maybe it's this way.
That's the other side!
You want me to take it?
Maybe it's that way.
Aaaaah!
This is a cool place.
Ta-da!
Hiroko.
It's written "hirogana" and reads "hirogana".
This is
This is hirogako.
I'm here in front of my father's boat and I'm going fishing now.
It's my first time to go squid fishing, so I'm not sure if it's different from normal fishing or not.
I'm looking forward to it!
The boat has sailed!
With the storm on the Sea of Japan at our backs
It's so big!
It feels so nice!
I can take it like this
It's light.
This is the weight.
When it's not on.
That's right.
When it's on.
It's supposed to be really stiff.
The tip of my tip...
The light came on.
The power's on.
It's 7:40, about 20 minutes from now.
When it's about 7:40...
Between 50 and 65.
Try to find between 50 and 65.
Still there.
fôngNh
f Feng
Good night.
Imitate, imitate, imitate.
It's a mess.
Nothing but a video...
Lamp av.
Day trip.
I see an image behind you.
Yes, it's hard.
I do Sher, it's coming up.
Yes!
No!
Yeah!
We did it!
Big boy!
I'm so happy!
Big!
That's so fun!
So much fun!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Oh! Wow!
Wow!
Oh, my gosh!
That's great!
Yeah!
Good call!
I got a good one!
That's the third one!
Yeah!
Wow! That's great!
That's the fourth one!
It feels heavy.
Like this!
Wow!
There you go!
How many?
Here?
Ah!
Aah!
We're back on land.
We made it to land.
So many squid!
Beautiful color
I'm going to cook this squid with my mom tomorrow
I'm going to cook some kind of squid
I want to eat it with my mother.
Now we are going to cook and eat the squid we caught yesterday!
What do you want to cook?
Squid sashimi.
You can make it plain, too.
You're right.
I love squid.
It's right here.
Do you have it?
It's got it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's got it right here.
Oh!
Wow.
I got it!
Oh, I'm watching the live broadcast of my prefectural tournament, on TV.
Go for it!
Baseball, huh?
Oh, yeah. High school baseball.
A!
Yes.
When I hear the theme song of Koshien, it reminds me of the summer of that year.
It reminds me of that summer.
You say that like it's a big deal.
It's not the theme song of Koshien anymore.
It's more like the theme song of that summer.
Oh!
Well done, for empathizing with me.
Yes, indeed.
Yes, it's open!
It's open.
It's so sharp.
Yeah, it's very sharp.
Dad, you ask a lot of questions.
It's a hobby.
I'm sure it'll be fun.
Now, get up.
What?
I can't cut the knife.
Oh, really?
Do you prefer the dooba?
Doba's better.
Yes, it's better.
When you're hungry, you cut your stomach.
Cut the incision
Finished
Cuttlefish
Squid with Tuna Mana Lens
We will eat the squid you caught by yourself
Looks delicious!
Let's eat it!
Delicious!
Delicious?
Yes, it is.
Sweet.
Bon appétit.
Let's eat together.
I'll have some, big brother.
Why?
Are you ashamed?
I don't want to be in it.
Is it good?
Try it with watermelon.
It's sweet.
With watermelon?
It's much tastier.
What's that?
What?
It's delicious.
I think you're overreacting.
I'm just trying to get a reaction.
Sumitama!
Always.
Delicious.
Delicious!
Come here.
Um...
She's going through puberty.
My sister is sleeping.
Good night, sweetie.
Yum. Yum.
Delicious.
Delicious!
Korean cold noodles sometimes have watermelon in them.
Ah, pears and watermelon...
I thought, "Oh, that means it has to be sour.
Oh, I see. Something with a sour taste.
Is this your mom's original?
Yes, ma'am.
Oh, it's a book.
Nice Orinzi.
I know.
It was delicious!
I just arrived at Tsuruga station
I'm going to take the Hokuriku Shinkansen back home now!
I was back home for 3 days and 2 nights.
I ate a lot of delicious food and had a lot of fun with my family.
I had a lot of fun with my family
I also got to meet my beloved cat!
It was really relaxing and fun!
I had a lot of experiences.
Thank you for watching!
I think it was a great homecoming!
I hope you all had a good time in Fukui Prefecture.
I hope you could feel the goodness of Mihama Town.
I would be very happy.
I rested a lot.
I made a lot of happy memories.
In August
I'm looking forward to Shikisei's Budokan live concert
and the Hyuga Festival
I will do my best!
Mizuki Hiraoka
Thank you for watching my return home.
Thank you very much!
Please subscribe to our channel and click the "Good" button
Bye bye!